and it's that it doesn't go wrong then.
After all, you control both yourself and
own equipment and then there is someone
other who controls the equipment
also.
Shall we check that the breathing resistance
works because there isn't much left
here. Now we just have to do tightness tests.
So and now is actually the device
clarified. Red jug have a very
complex service. They must be able to
everything you can do on land with
ammunition clearance. But they have to
be able to dive and take care of things below
the water.
>> We're going to putty a screw jet.
>> Yes.
>> And that's a bit of your domain eh one
directed blasting that works under
water.
>> Yes.
>> Eh preps it with puff pastry. Eh pressing
in there. This is such a form of charging
which we are doing at Svedäck when we
filled charging molds and shot at different ones
object. So this is also a form of
charging form that you then fill with
explosives themselves so and so you create
some form of directed blasting. The
here you can my role here today is
to be a dive leader. The dive leader's role is